Seat's all mine!
You jerk!
There's room next to me.
Wanna sit?
Actually, I'll stand.
Yeah? Okay.
He seriously doesn't have a clue!
He doesn't treat me anything like a girl,
and I'm always the only one
who's all hyper-aware.
Even though my heart's pounding so hard...
I feel so stupid!
Tomo's
Skirt
"Tomo's Skirt."
It's getting pretty crowded.
Wh-What?! Is this what they call a groper?!
Wait, that couldn't happen
to me of all people...
He just groped me?!
I just wanna slug him right now!
But...
I'm not sure why, but I don't
want Jun to know about this.
This is so gross.
I feel like I have to just put
up with it, or I'll start crying.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Jun took care of everything,
from reporting the guy
to handing him over to the authorities.
Lock him up for life, please.
Tomo, you okay?
Oh... Yeah...
Be sure to go talk to the police later.
I've never seen Jun like this before.
Gonna be a pain in the ass, but...
I feel like he's actually treating
me like a girl right now.
Also, you know...
Hey! Are you listening?
Huh? Wh-What's up?
I was saying...
Maybe you should stop wearing skirts.
Huh?
What did you just say?
When I got groped on the
bus yesterday, Jun said—
What's this about groping?
What did he do to you? Are you okay?
Oh... Yeah...
He just touched my butt a little.
Did you take him to the police?
You didn't let him go, did you?
Jun took care of all that.
I see.
Uh... Misuzu?
Anyway, what were you saying about him?
Huh? Oh...
Well, he said...
What the hell are you saying?
Our school allows girls to wear slacks, too.
Why not wear those?
But why are you suddenly
bringing this up now?
Why? Because...
It...
It looks wrong on you!
And I can't relax when you're wearing it.
I know damn well it looks wrong on me!
Jun, you asshole!
Just when I thought he was finally
treating me like a girl!
That jerk!
I see.
But if you think about the circumstances,
he may have said it because he doesn't
want you getting groped again.
Huh?
You mean he was thinking about me that way?
Jun was?
I'm sorry. That was an
irresponsible thing to say.
No?! So there's no chance of that at all?!
Anyway, I noticed a while ago,
but hadn't said anything...
Your skirt is pretty short.
I didn't think you were the type
to enjoy showing that much leg.
Why do you wear it so short?
Well, 'cause it's easier to move around in.
What other reason would there be?
Yeah, skirts really aren't meant for you.
For starters...
Try taking off the shorts for a while.
What?! No way!
What are you getting all pervy for?!
I'm not.
Look, Tomo...
The normal way to wear a skirt is with
nothing but your panties underneath.
You liar!
If your skirt flipped up,
people would see everything!
That's what skirts are.
Even I...
only have panties on under mine today.
Huh?!
That's the kind of girl you are?
I haven't done anything to
deserve that creeped-out look.
Junichiro.
Huh?
I heard what happened.
You had a fight with Tomo, huh?
Lay off.
Tomo says she wants to walk home with you.
She's waiting downstairs.
You'd better go now.
For real?! She's not mad anymore?!
That's right.
Sweet!
Hey, Jun.
Let's walk home together.
Jun?!
Let's go.
Y-Yeah...
Just try going without the shorts for now.
I bet that'll get a different
reaction out of Junichiro.
I ended up taking them off like Misuzu said.
Hey, Jun...
Sorry I hit you so hard yesterday.
Okay?
She's right. Jun's reacting totally
differently than he has before.
Huh?
Jun?!
In fact, he's being just plain weird!
Standing room only again?
This bus is always packed lately.
Junichiro Vision
Jun's walking faster than usual today.
Hey, Jun!
What's his problem?
It's almost like he's
running away from me.
Wait up, would you?!
Jun?!
Sorry.
Huh?
Something was wrong with me yesterday.
I know just being best buds doesn't give me
the right to tell you to dress differently.
But...
I don't think it's right to wear
stuff that you feel embarrassed in.
It messes things up for me, too.
Jun's making such an interesting face!
Are you even listening to me?
How'd it go after you took
off the shorts yesterday?
It went horribly! That's how!
I'm never dressing like that again!
Did he see your panties?
Bull's-eye.
Okay, and how did Junichiro react?
Actually, I don't really know why, but...
He dropped like a rock.
I hear you haven't said
a word to Tomo all day.
She seemed pretty sad.
Shut up.
It's unusual for you to
avoid Tomo for half a day.
I guess it'll take a while for
you to reset this time, huh?
Go on, try—
Heya, Tomo! Let's eat lunch together!
Jun!
I keep telling you not to pop
up outta nowhere like that!
Aw, don't be mean!
I'm not!
I'm just acting like I always do!
It'll be interesting to see
how long this keeps up.
See? See? See? See?
You little—
The School Idol
"The School Idol."
Good morning, Carol-chan!
Morning.
You look as cute as ever!
Can I carry your bag for you?
No, thanks.
There she is. Carol Olston.
Surrounded from the moment she
shows up, just like every day.
If she's the most popular with the guys,
does that mean she's the girliest?
It's hard to say.
Must be nice... How do
you even get that way?
For starters...
Put down the dumbbell.
She's not just popular for her looks.
She's also the only English student in the
school, so she has a certain premium feel.
Also...
What?
Her personality.
That soft, defenseless feel she has
hits the guys right in their instincts.
What, so being defenseless is good?
Someone like that would get
knocked out in no time!
You should really stop thinking
in terms of knocking people out.
How can being defenseless
actually be better?
If I make friends with
that cotton candy chick,
will I find out?
Aizawa-san!
What's wrong? You look lost in thought.
Misaki-senpai...
Whoa! Cotton Candy!
Cotton Candy?
What are you two doing together?
She's a distant relative of mine.
You could say we've been friends
since we were little... or...
We're engaged.
Engaged?!
Are you... serious?
You two are getting married someday?
It has been discussed, I guess...
We've already gotten married.
Three times.
She's talking about when we were kids,
pretending to get married!
Anyway, are you a friend of Carol's?
No, we haven't really talked much,
but we're in the same class.
Right?
You don't remember?
Dunno.
I'm not interested in the boys in our class.
I'm a girl! Do you not see the skirt?!
S-Sorry! I'm so sorry!
She's a little strange,
but she doesn't mean any harm,
so let it slide, okay?
Well, if you say so, Senpai.
Thanks, Aizawa-san.
You're a really nice person.
Huh? Not really...
A girl...
Poke!
She doesn't... mean any harm, right?
Hey... Come on, Carol!
Dummy.
So... what's that all about?
That's what I wanna know.
I only talked to her for
the first time today,
but she's apparently
Misaki-senpai's fiancée.
Ah, I get it.
And Senpai was with you when
you talked to her, wasn't he?
Yeah, he was.
And you have no idea why she picked
a fight with you in that situation?
Right. I don't remember doing anything.
Dummy.
Why are you doing that now, too?!
Misuzu-chan, Misuzu-chan.
There's something I want
to talk to you about.
Fine...
But first, get off my desk.
Okay.
Let's get this out of the way first.
I'm not fond of people like you.
Okay, got it.
I want to ask you some
questions about Tomo-chan.
You're tough.
You seem to see Tomo as your enemy,
but no matter what you might think,
I consider myself her best friend.
If you're trying to dig up dirt,
ask someone else.
Even if I'd treat you to cake? It's tasty...
I'll hear you out, at least.
Okay, so...
How do you think I can defeat Tomo-chan?
At least try to cover up
your malice a little bit.
Now, I wonder how I can use this girl.
If that's what you want to know...
There's someone else who
can help you more than me.
Hey, who's your favorite girl in first year?
Carol-chan, obviously!
She's as cute as a doll!
Mine's Misuzu-chan! I love those icy eyes!
Hi.
Are you Kubota Junichiro?
Yeah, that's me.
There's something I want
to talk to you about.
Boys' Locker Room
First of all...
Get out of my locker.
I said there was someone I want to defeat,
and I was referred to you.
So Gundo sent you, huh?
I don't really like that, but...
I'm surprised there's someone besides
her who'd want to beat someone up.
I was just looking for a way to kill
time while my buddy's doing club stuff.
I'll help pump you up if you
can meet me after school.
Pump me up?
First, let's see you hit
me as hard as you can.
Like this?
I was hoping you'd hit my hand, actually...
Anyway, you're pretty damn weak, aren't you?
A kitten could beat you up.
Are you going to make me stronger?
Well, it depends on how far you're
willing to go, but give me a month.
I'll get you to bear cub level, at least.
Are those strong?
Yo, let's go, Blondie.
My name isn't Blondie.
It's Carol.
Whatever. Just come on.
'Kay!
Yes, I know.
Did you see that?! What was that about?!
Why is Jun acting like that with her?!
I don't know, but...
It's obvious that something happened.
For Junichiro to be like that
with a girl who isn't you...
Maybe they're actually...
No! No way!
I mean, she has a fiancé!
Wait, but... maybe...
That's right, Tomo.
That's the sense of urgency
that you need more of.
Okay, we're gonna start by running.
'Kay!
What's wrong?
I can't run any more.
Are you kidding me?
I wonder...
what Jun and that girl
are up to right now...
Jun...
A-Aizawa-san...
Captain!
Next is strength training.
'Kay!
One...
I can't.
Look... What can you do?
I can jump rope.
'Cause I like bunnies.
Okay, I don't know what
that means, but go for it.
Why are you looking up?
Neck exercise!
Jun! This is where you've...
been...
Okay, when your enemy comes
up on you like this...
Hey, there's my enemy!
You were talking about Tomo?!
She's really strong, though!
Wha...
What the hell are you guys doing?!
I asked you what you're doing, damn it!
H-Hey... What are you so mad about?
I'm not mad! I'm just asking!
Just stick close to him,
and you'll find out in no time.
Assuming you're not a total idiot, that is.
I lose.
Tomo-chan, Tomo-chan.
I'm done being your enemy now, okay?
Huh?
I'm done with this training, too.
Bye-bye!
I came along because you promised
to treat me to cake...
But why are we in this
unnecessarily long car?
And who is that guy in the black suit?
I dunno.
You're the one who called him.
There are lots of guys in black suits
at my house whose names I don't know.
Don't you have any at your house?
I'm pretty sure most people don't.
Hey, so, Misuzu-chan...
Since we're eating cake together,
does that mean we're friends now?
I'm not sure.
Do you want friends?
Yeah!
I don't have even a single friend.
Dunno why.
Indeed, I wonder why.
If you want friends,
you should talk to Tomo.
I'm sure she'd be your friend.
And it would be a great
motivator for Tomo, too.
Hmm... I did a lot of mean
things to her, though.
So you do feel bad about it, then?
That doesn't matter, though.
She's nice to a fault toward
anyone who approaches her.
She calls a girl like me
her best friend, after all.
I see...
Even despite your bad personality, huh?
That's exactly your problem.
Hey, Tomo-chan!
Oh, it's you. What is it now?
Well...
Fwiend!
Ew, no way.
Friends?
Uh, I dunno...
Let's not...
Um... It's kind of hard to say, but...
Th-There's something that's
hard for her to say?
What kind of crazy thing
is she about to say?!
I want you to be my friend!
Huh?
Oh, sure, that's fine.
Jeez, that's what you wanted?
I didn't know what I was gonna do
if you called me your enemy again.
Okay, well... nice to know ya!
Tomo-chan, you're...
just like an angel!
Huh? An a-angel?!
Misuzu-chan, will you be my friend, too?
Fine with me.
You seem to be pretty rich, after all.
Yay!
I'm so glad I'm rich!
I never thought I'd end up
being friends with her.
She's pretty nice once you
talk to her a little.
Huh...
That blonde and Gundo are apparently
pretty popular with the guys.
Well, they're both cute and girly, I guess.
Are they?
Well, not that I'm in any place
to say much about Gundo...
Huh?!
Wait, are you saying you
have a thing for Misuzu?!
Hell no.
You know we went out for a
while in middle school, right?
Huh?